In this Kolo 2026.0 update, we have optimized the
Kolo 2026.0 with this new Kolo 2026.0 and the new Kolo 2026.0 after the update.
The Kolo 2026.0 line of actions is also approved by the Kolo 2026.0.
Kolo 2026.0 is a short drive, so it can be processed in a very short time.
When you click the XML file button, you can go to the Zip file, and a blank space will
appear.
After searching, you will see the Zip file located in the Zip.
Click the left mouse button to confirm the measurement point on the board.
At this time, the 2D window will display the measurement line in a virtual form.
Please note that the data will be recorded immediately in the custom measurement part of the property editor.
You can rename the measurement line here.
Change the visibility of the line or delete it completely.
At the bottom, you can see an option to lock.
You can choose to lock the outline line or the outline of the board.
At this time, I need the measurement value to be locked on the outline of the board.
After moving the sticker, you can see that the measurement line is locked at the HPS point.
You can enter the specific data value below to accurately control the position of the sticker.
Next, we will try the second method.
Lock the measurement line starting from the outline line outside the sticker.
Also, after selecting the sticker, right-click and select the custom measurement.
This time, the outline line outside the sticker is directly left-clicked.
You will see a purple line extending to the outline of the board.
When you stop the mouse on the outline line, the length of the measurement will be moved.
Left-click the outline line to set the measurement point.
This purple line is the measurement line from a certain point of the sticker to a certain point of the outline line.
These two points are all set.
In the same way, you can rename and adjust the value of the x-axis and y-axis positions in the attribute editor.
Enter the value of the specific x-axis and y-axis to get the exact position of the sticker.
If you need to measure from the specific point inside the sticker instead of the outline line, you can use the Shift key shortcut.
As before, enter the custom measurement mode.
Press the Shift key and click on any point in the picture.
For example, the end point or specific detail point of the outline.
We automatically recognize these points.
Select the target point on the sticker.
There is a certain subtraction function when selecting.
This flexibility allows you to record measurement information from any position in the picture.
For example, I chose this recommended pivot point in the picture.
Then measure the distance from the point to the side.
You can also enter a specific value in the attribute editor.
Accurate positioning of the sticker.
Finally, we updated the 3D window interface.
Now you can quickly hide or display stickers.
To check the basic principle of clothing,
All you have to do is go to the menu bar and navigate to the clothing display.
Then open or close the display sticker.
We hope that this sticker measurement function update can ensure that your sticker position is always accurate.